A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3 FA456
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 3; 10.8 Cubic Feet 9 record storage cartons.
  - Cornerstone Baptist Church, Brooklyn, NY, 1966 May 29 (Box 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller at Cornerstone Baptist Church, Brooklyn NY and Hotel Hilton NY Elks meeting, 1966 May 29; 1008.15/Roll529A-529D (Box 6)
      - Governor at Elks meeting..., 1008.15/Roll529C-529D (Box 6)
        - Governor and Zelma E. Young, New York State President of the order (Roll 529C, Frame 12)
        - Governor poses as he leaves the Elks meeting, mostly the "security guard" of the Elks (Roll 529D, Frame 1-3)
  - Hunter College. NY City, 1966 June 1 (Box 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller attends the one hundred and seventh Commencement ceremony of New York Medical College, Hunter College Auditorium, 1966 June 1; 1008.15/Roll61A-61B (Box 6)
      - 7 months old Leonard Charles Turano and his mother Judith of Jamaica, Queens (Roll 61A, Frame 1)
      - Dr. Laurence Slobody, Vice President and Acting Dean, Mrs. Jackson E. Spears, Chairman of the Board of Trustees (Roll 61A, Frame 2-4)
      - General View showing Happy (Roll 61A, Frame 5)
      - Governor addressing audience (Roll 61A, Frame 6-10)
      - unidentified (Roll 61B, Frame 1-4)
      - Governor receives Honorary Degree of Dr. of Humane Letters (Roll 61B, Frame 5-7)
      - Jackson E. Spears, Governor Rockefeller, Mrs. Rockefeller, Dr. Colin Macleod, Deputy Director, Office of Science and Technology, Executive Office of the President of the United States, who also received Doctor of Humane Letters Degree (Roll 61B, Frame 8-9)
  - Buffalo, NY, Governors' Conference, 1966 June 2 (Box 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller at Buffalo NY, 1966 June 2-3; 1008.15/Roll62A-62C (Box 6)
      - Governors Conference on Manpower Training at Statler Hilton Hotel (Roll 62A)
        - Left to right... Honorable L.R. Peterson, minister of Labor and Education, British Columbia, Canada. Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller Bertil Olsson, Director General, National Labor Market Board, Sweden and M.P. Catherwood, Industrial Commissioner of New York State (Roll 62A, Frame 1)
        - Governor speaking at the first day session of the conference, left to right are...Mayor Frank Sedita of Buffalo. Governor...Caterwood... Samuel Gould and James Allen Jr (Roll 62A, Frame 3-6)
        - left to right Samuel B. Gould, President State University of NY James E. Allen Jr. Commissioner of Education of State of NY Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller (Roll 62A, Frame 8-10)
      - Governor at press conference, Manpower Conference Buffalo NY (Roll 62B, Frame 1-2)
      - Governor Rockefeller and Harry Van Arsdale At Washington DC Conference with Congressmen and Javitts (Roll 62B, Frame 3)
      - Senator Javitts and Governor Rockefeller before the conference (Roll 62B, Frame 5-8)
      - Governor speaking at press session after conference (Roll 62B, Frame 9-10)
      - At Willard NY/en route to Dresden NY for Yates County Rep. Comm. Dinner (Box 6)
        - Signing autographs for youngsters at the dock in Willard NY before boarding cruiser for trip across Lake Seneca (Roll 62C, Frame 1-3)
        - The Governor is greeted by Fred Dugan, Congressional Candidate as he arrived at boat for trip to Dresden (Roll 62C, Frame 4-5)
        - Governor with Fred Dugan (Roll 62C, Frame 6)
        - The Governor waves to people on Dresden dock as cruiser arrives. with him is Fred Dugan (Roll 62C, Frame 7)
        - Left to Right... on dock at Dresden NY, Fred Dugan...Mayor of Elmira, NY Governor Rockefeller and Robert Rose of Elmira (Roll 62C, Frame 8-9)
        - Fred Dugan and Governor Rockefeller march between flags at Dresden NY (Roll 62C, Frame 10)
  - Dresden. NY, 1008.15/Roll62D; (10) (Box 6)
    - Marching with Fred Dugan at Dresden NY (Roll 62D, Frame 1)
    - Governor greets Jean Ferguson of Penn Yan NY, a member of the Penn Yan Academy Marching Band. Band leader is at right (Roll 62D, Frame 3)
    - Governor making presentation to Mrs. Ruth G. Conley of Penn Yan NY, daughter of 94 year old Benjamin F. Gardner (Roll 62D, Frame 5)
    - Governor making presentation to Lynn H. Carpenter, former Yates County Chairman (Roll 62D, Frame 4)
    - Governor with gifts from Seneca Wine... Charles L. Wallis, County Chairman and Fred Dugan are in pic (Roll 62D, Frame 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller as he rose to speak at Dresden (Roll 62D, Frame 7)
    - Governor speaking at Dresden (Roll 62D, Frame 9)
    - Governor with Robert Rose in cabin of cruiser on Lake Seneca (Roll 62D, Frame 10)
    - Governor thanks Trooper W.V. Rice of Waterloo NY (Roll 62D, Frame 11)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1966 June 3; 1008.15/Roll63A-63B (Box 6)
    - Governors Conference on Manpower at the Statler Hilton Hotel
      - The dais at Friday morning session of the conf (Roll 63A, Frame 1)
      - Left to Right Governor Rockefeller, Dr. Jerome H. Holland, President of Hampton Inst. (Roll 63A, Frame 2-4)
    - Henery T. Heald, Chairman of the Friday morning session (Roll 63B, Frame 1-3)
    - Governor signs the NY State Manpower Training Act at the closing luncheon of the conference of Manpower Training in Buffalo NY Seated are.. .Governor.. .and Dr. Jerome H. Holland President of Hampton Inst. Standing are... left to right... Leo Kreigbaum, representative International Building Services of Buffalo... Thomas Hopkin business Manager Local 17, International union of Operating and Professional Employees International Union Council of NY... Not in every negative... Harrold Dalton, Director Region One International Union of Operating Engineers (Roll 63B, Frame 5)
    - Governor Rockefeller speaking at the luncheon (Roll 63B, Frame 6-7)
    - Local dignitary at Buffalo NY (Roll 63B, Frame 8)
    - Left to Right.. .Governor with Troopers Ruehl and Gibbs of Clarence NY Barracks (Roll 63B, Frame 9)
  - NY City, 1966 June 4 (Box 6)
    - Roll64A, 1008.15/Roll64A; (11)
    - Roll 64B, 1008.15/Roll64B; (4) (Box 6)
  - Syracuse University, 1966 June 5 (Box 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller at Syracuse NY, 1966 June 5; 1008.15/Roll65A-65C (Box 6)
      - Syracuse University 112th Commencement...
        - left to right... Chancellor William Pearson Tolley of Syracuse University.. Mrs. Edwin A. Link of Binghamton NY a Trustee of Syracuse U. and Governor (Roll 65A, Frame 1)
        - The Honorary degree recipients: left to right - Knox, Link, Governor Rockefeller, Chancellor Tolley, Stevens, Bynum, Dineen, Shirley (Roll 65A, Frame 2)
        - Seated are Governor R. Chancellor Tolley, Dean Shirley standing, Knox, Levy, Link, Stevens, Bynum, Dineen (Roll 65A, Frame 3-4)
        - Chancellor Tolley and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 65A, Frame 5-6)
        - Governor Rockefeller in the academic procession (Roll 65A, Frame 7-9)
        - Governor Rockefeller delivering the main address at Syracuse Commencement (Roll 65B, Frame 2-3)
      - Branch office of Governor Rockefeller PR Department at Syracuse, Sunday 6/5 temperature near 90 degrees, 1966 June 5 (Roll 65B, Frame 5)
      - Governor Rockefeller receives honorary degree. Chancellor Telley at left (Roll 65B, Frame 6-8)
      - Governor is congratulated after receiving degree, other person unknown (Roll 65B, Frame 9)
      - Chancellor Tolley and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 65B, Frame 10)
      - Governor and Chancellor in academic procession (Roll 65C, Frame 1)
      - Governor Rockefeller and Mayor Walsh of Syracuse (Roll 65C, Frame 2)
      - Governor with Sara Ann Siegler of Levittown NY and her mother. Miss Siegler thanked Governor for Regents Scholarship that enabled her to graduate from Syracuse with Liberal Arts degree today (Roll 65C, Frame 3)
      - Governor with possible local candidate, will get ident on this (Roll 65C, Frame 4-5)
  - Garden City. NY, 1966 June 7; 1008.15/Roll67A; (20) (Box 6)
    - Long Island 200 BEV Accelerator Information Luncheon at the Sky Club, Roosevelt Field (Roll 67A)
      - Toby Colletti, Pres of the LI Federation of Labor with the Governor at the Luncheon (Roll 67A, Frame 1)
      - Governor Rockefeller speaking at the luncheon (Roll 67A, Frame 3-4)
      - Governor talks to press after luncheon (Roll 67A, Frame 5)
      - Governor greets unknown man after luncheon (Roll 67A, Frame 6)
      - Left to Right... Tony Colletti, Pres LI Fed. of Labor H. Lee Dennison, Suffolk County Exec, and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 67A, Frame 7-8)
      - Governor Rockefeller greets Sol Newban (check spelling) Receiver of Taxes Town of Oyster Bay. Unidentified Newsman in center (Roll 67A, Frame 9)
      - Governor talk to Peter Brennan (labor leader) after luncheon (Roll 67A, Frame 10)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs bill for Teachers Annuity Program, 1966 June 7; 1008.15/1748 1008.15/1749 (Box 6)
  - NY City, 1966 June 8 (Box 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller In NY City, 1966 June 8-9; 1008.15/Roll68A-69K (Box 6)
      - Swearing In of Judge William S. Shea all negatives show swearing-in ceremony and the family of Judge Shea (Roll 68A)
      - Special servicing instruction were given with film... NY City papers and the local Irish Catholic and area newspapers. Press conference at the Hotel Hilton on the New York City tax program (Roll 68A)
      - all negatives show Governor Rockefeller speaking to radio, TV and news men (Roll 68B)
      - At Water Pollution Control Conference at the Hotel Hilton (Roll 68B)
      - Governor talks to James H. Gavin a construction worker who talked to Governor for few moments (Roll 68C, Frame 1)
      - Governor as he started to speak, at his left is Ross Frazer chairman of Board Associated Industries (Roll 68C, Frame 2)
      - Governor speaking at the conference (Roll 68C, Frame 3-4)
      - Left to Right... James Kussmann of St. Regis Paper...Governor Rockefeller...Ross Frazer and unidentified man (Roll 68C, Frame 5)
      - Governor and Ross Frazer leave the conference (Roll 68C, Frame 6-7)
      - leaving conference... Governor stops to talk to Secretary of State Lomenzo (Roll 68C, Frame 8)
      - Governor Rockefeller and Nicaraguan President Dr. Rene Schick Gutierrez, at the Waldorf Towers... (Box 6)
        - Governor and Nicaraguan Ambassador (Roll 68D, Frame 1)
        - Governor Rockefeller...unidentified man and Pres Gutierrez (Roll 68D, Frame 2)
        - the Governor with President (Roll 68D, Frame 3-9)
      - at the Suffolk county Republican Committee Breakfast at the Hotel Hilton... (Box 6)
        - Suffolk County Chairman Robert A. Curcio and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 69A, Frame 1)
        - Governor greeting Suffolk County Committee members (Roll 69A, Frame 2-10)
        - Brooklyn Chairman Cruise and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 69A, Frame 11)
        - unidentified man... Mrs. Wilma C. Rogalin and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 69A, Frame 12)
      - local candidates with Governor (Roll 69B, Frame 1)
      - Governor talks to Brooklyn leader Cruise (Roll 69B, Frame 2)
      - Governor as he waved to the Suffolk County Rep. Committee (Roll 69B, Frame 3)
      - Governor speaking (Roll 69B, Frame 4-5)
      - Mrs. Wilma C. Rogalin and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 69C, Frame 1)
      - Lt Governor Malcolm Wilson and Governor (Roll 69C, Frame 2)
      - Minority Leader Perry B. Duryea Jr.. Lt. Governor Malcolm Wilson and Governor (Roll 69C, Frame 3)
      - Governor and Edward McGowan, Master of Ceremonies (Roll 69C, Frame 4)
      - Lt Governor Wilson and Carl Spad (Roll 69C, Frame 5)
      - Mrs. Rogalin and Secretary of State Lomenzo (Roll 69C, Frame 6)
      - Lt Governor Wilson and Carl Spad (Roll 69C, Frame 7)
      - Perry Duryea and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 69C, Frame 8)
      - Attorney General Lefkowitz and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 69C, Frame 9-10)
      - untitled (Roll 69C, Frame 11)
      - unidentified (Roll 69F, Frame 1)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller (Roll 69F, Frame 2)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller with several members of the Rockettes (Roll 69F, Frame 3)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller with campaign workers (Roll 69F, Frame 4)
      - Governor greets Mrs. Alice Mitchell. (Roll 69F, Frame 5)
      - Governor greets friends at luncheon (Roll 69F, Frame 6-7)
      - Governor and Mrs. Miriam Girard, City Campaign Co-Director (Roll 69F, Frame 8-9)
      - Governor and Mrs. Gladys Hamilton, State Campaign Co-Director (Roll 69F, Frame 10)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller (Roll 69G, Frame 1-3)
      - at International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers reception at Hotel New Yorker (Roll 69G, Frame 4)
      - Governor with Harry Van Arsdale Jr. (Roll 69G, Frame 5)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller with group of officials at Electrical Workers reception (Roll 69G, Frame 6-7)
      - Left to Right... Edward Rivers Sr,. President Lewis Howard, Latimer Progressive Association, Governor Rockefeller, Harry Van Arsdale Jr. (Roll 69G, Frame 8)
      - Governor with members of the Electrical Group. Local 3 (Roll 69G, Frame 9)
      - Governor is escorted into/Electrical Workers meeting at Manhattan Center (Roll 69G, Frame 10)
      - Governor at Local 3 Meeting, left to right... Jeremiah P. Sullivan, former Pres of the local, Governor Rockefeller and Edward J. Cleary, President of Local 3 (Roll 69G, Frame 11)
      - Governor Rockefeller waves to Local 3 meeting, with him is Harry Van Arsdale Jr. (Roll 69G, Frame 12)
      - at Republican State Dinner, Waldorf Astoria, Neg #s start at 5 (Box 6)
        - Mrs. Rockefeller, Governor, unidentified woman, and Mrs. Rogalin (Roll 69H, Frame 5)
        - Governor and Commissioner McHugh (Roll 69H, Frame 6)
        - untitled (Roll 69H, Frame 7)
        - left to right, Attorney General Lefkowitz, Governor, Senator Spino, and Lt Governor Wilson (Roll 69H, Frame 8)
        - Commissioner McHugh and Mike (Roll 69H, Frame 9)
        - Former Governor Dewey, Mrs. Dewey and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 69H, Frame 10-11)
      - Republican State Dinner, Waldorf (Box 6)
        - Left to Right, Jackie Robinson, Governor, Mrs. Robinson and unidentified man (Roll 69J, Frame 1)
        - Governor Dewey, Lt. Governor Wilson and ? (Roll 69J, Frame 2)
        - W.H. Anderson, E.W. Bryges and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 69J, Frame 3)
        - Former Governor Dewey, Mrs. Rockefeller and Carl Spad (Roll 69J, Frame 4)
        - Governor and Lt Governor as they spoke in the small dining rooms at dinner (Roll 69J, Frame 5-8)
        - Governor meets four of the Vietnam wounded from St. Albans Hospital left to right.. Governor Rockefeller, PFC Tony Oliva (partly hidden by Governor) Cpl. Thomas Marchesell, Pfc Roger Klaus and HM3 Pat Piccininni (Roll 69J, Frame 9)
        - Carl Spad speaking at the dinner (Roll 69J, Frame 10)
      - at Republican State Dinner, Waldorf (Box 6)
        - Governor applauds former Governor Dewey as he rose to speak (Roll 69K, Frame 1)
        - Mayor Lindsay speaking (Roll 69K, Frame 3)
        - Neg shows Governor shaking hands with Mayor Lindsay (Newsphoto has this eg) (Roll 69K, Frame 4)
        - Governor Rockefeller greet diners (Roll 69K, Frame 5)
        - Governor speaking (Roll 69K, Frame 6-7)
        - Governor with Mrs. Lindsay (Roll 69K, Frame 8-9)
        - Senator Javits, Mayor Lindsay and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 69K, Frame 10)
        - Mrs. and Governor Rockefeller and Mrs. Rogalin (Roll 69K, Frame 11)
  - Red Room. atomic energy 200 BEV Accelerator bill, 1966 June 15; 1008.15/1750 (Box 6)
  - Saratoga Springs, NY, 1966 June 16; 1008.15/Roll616A-616D (Box 6)
    - At hall of Springs for luncheon of Performing Arts Center Board of Directors (Roll 616A)
      - Governor greets Hall of Springs chefs, left to right are Kenneth Olesen, General Manager of restaurant, (back to camera) Governor Rockefeller, Syd Olesen and Harry Tidholm (Roll 616A, Frame 1)
      - Governor at buffet table the Governor took time out from luncheon to visit conservation dept. picnic (Roll 616A, Frame 2)
      - Governor greets Conservation Department picnickers (Roll 616A, Frame 3-4)
      - Governor with Mrs. Laura T. Heineman, Conservation Department employee (Roll 616A, Frame 5)
      - Governor and Conservation Commissioner Kilborne t buffet in Hall of Springs, Chef in Syd Olesen (Roll 616A, Frame 6)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller walk in rain to Performing Arts Center Amphitheater for dedication ceremonies, with them is Gene Robb (check) (Roll 616A, Frame 7-9)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller greet workmen (unidentified) at the performing Arts Amphitheater (Roll 616A, Frame 10)
    - Untitled (Roll 616A)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller inspect stage of the Performing Arts Center Amphitheater (Roll 616B, Frame 1-3)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller and Gene Robb, in Green Room of Performing Arts Center (Roll 616B, Frame 4-6)
      - The dedication of ceremony at the amphitheater (Roll 616B, Frame 7)
      - Gene Robb speaking (Roll 616B, Frame 8)
      - Plaque is given to Mrs. Rockefeller for presentation to Governor (Roll 616B, Frame 9)
      - Mrs. Rockefeller presents plaque to Governor (Roll 616B, Frame 10)
      - Governor is congratulated by Joseph H. Murphy, Commissioner of Taxation and Finance (Roll 616B, Frame 11)
      - Governor speaking at the dedication of the Performing Arts Center Amphitheater (Roll 616C, Frame 1)
      - Mrs. Rockefeller is given roses by Gerald Strait, Construction Superintendent of project (Roll 616C, Frame 2)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller after the dedication of the Amphitheater (Roll 616C, Frame 3-6)
      - Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller with roses given by the construction workers (Roll 616C, Frame 7)
      - Governor signing autographs after ceremony (Roll 616C, Frame 8)
      - Mrs. Rockefeller is surrounded by admirers after ceremony (Roll 616C, Frame 9-10)
      - Mrs. Rockefeller signs autographs after Amphitheater dedication (Roll 616, Frame 1-4)
      - Governor greets Pipe Major James Walsh of Schenectady Pipe Band (Roll 616, Frame 5)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller with (left) Pipe Major James Walsh and Drum Major Ian MacLean of Schenectady Pipe Band (Roll 616, Frame 6-7D)
  - New York City, 1966 June 18 (Box 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller in NY City, 1966 June 18; 1008.15/Roll618A-618B (Box 6)
      - At the Bronx County Republican Committee Dinner, Concourse Plaza, NY (Roll 618A)
        - Left to Right, Congressman Paul A Fino and Mrs. Fino with Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller (Roll 618A, Frame 1-2)
        - Left to right, Congressman Fino, Governor Rockefeller and Senator John. D. Calandra (Roll 618A, Frame 3-4)
        - Congressman Fino, Governor Rockefeller and Terence P Dolan, Financial Secretary of uniformed Fireman's Association (Roll 618A, Frame 5)
        - Left to Right, Congressman Fino, Governor Rockefeller and Bernard Beackon, candidate for Assemblyman 84th district (Roll 618A, Frame 6)
        - Left to Right, Attorney General Louis Lefkowitz, Governor Rockefeller and Congressman Fino (Roll 618A, Frame 7)
        - Staff personnel at Bronx Rep. dinner (Roll 618A, Frame 8)
        - Governor waves to audience before speech (Roll 618A, Frame 9)
      - at Rose Ball of the Association for the Help of Retarded Children at New York Hilton Hotel (Roll 618B)
        - Governor Rockefeller with the award presented by the Association, in center is Mrs. Allan Kaplan, at right the artist Mrs. Monte Belden (Roll 618B, Frame 1-2)
        - Left to Right. Governor Rockefeller, unidentified and Elliot L. Aronin President of Association (Roll 618B, Frame 3)
        - Governor Rockefeller and Elliot L. Aronin, Pres of the Association (Roll 618B, Frame 4)
        - Governor Rockefeller, two unidentified men and Elliot L Aronin (Roll 618B, Frame 5)
        - Mrs. Rockefeller (Roll 618B, Frame 5)
    - Roll 621A, 1966 June 21; 1008.15/Roll621A; (11) (Box 6)
    - Roll 621B, 1008.15/Roll621B; (11) (Box 6)
    - Roll 621C, 1008.15/Roll621C; (12) (Box 6)
    - Roll 621D, 1008.15/Roll621D; (10) (Box 6)
    - Roll 621E, 1008.15/Roll621E; (11) (Box 6)
    - Roll 621F, 1008.15/Roll621F; (11) (Box 6)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman McFarland, 1966 June 21; 1008.15/1751 - 1008.15/1752 (Box 6)
  - Red Room. bill signing, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Marks, Senator Laurance, 1966 June 21; 1008.15/1753 (Box 6)
  - Red Room. Bill signing, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 June 21; 1008.15/1754 - 1008.15/1755 (Box 6)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller bill signing, Thomas F. McCoy, Malachy T. Mahon, Peter Preiser, Paul McGinnis, Russell Oswald, Elliot Lombard, Milton Luger, 1966 June 21; 1008.15/1756 (Box 6)
  - New York City, 1966 June 22; 1008.15/Roll622A-622C (Box 6)
    - Announcement of Department of Commerce office opening in Tokyo (Roll 622A)
      - Left to right, Governor Rockefeller, Commissioner Keith S. McHugh of NY State Department of Commerce and Japanese Ambassador to the US Ryuji Takeuchi (Roll 622A, Frame 1-4)
      - Commissioner McHugh speaking at the reception (Roll 622A, Frame 5)
      - Governor Rockefeller speaking at the reception, at left are Commissioner McHugh and Japanese Ambassador (Roll 622A, Frame 6-9)
    - All negatives show Governor Rockefeller, Commissioner McHugh and Japanese Ambassador Ryuji Takeuchi at the reception and press conference EXCEPT-622B-6 that shows David Rockefeller and Japanese Ambassador (Roll 622B)
    - Left to right, Commissioner McHugh Mayor John F. Lindsay of New York City, Jap. Ambassador Ryuji Takeuchi and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 622C, Frame 1-2)
    - Mayor Lindsay speaking at the press conference (Roll 622C, Frame 3-4)
  - Rochester, NY, 1966 June 23; 1008.15/Roll623A-623B (Box 6)
    - Attends State Convention dinner VFW (Roll 623A)
      - Governor is greeted by Vincent J. DiMattina, Dept Comdr of VFW at Rochester airport (Roll 623A, Frame 1)
      - Governor talks to DiMattina and other VFW officers at the airport (Roll 623A, Frame 2)
      - Governor greets veterans and friends in front of Sheraton Hotel (Roll 623A, Frame 3)
      - TV interview in front of Sheraton Hotel, Rochester (Roll 623A, Frame 4)
      - Governor with two Rochester veterans, Sam Polatti and Tony Farisi. (Roll 623A, Frame 5)
      - left to right, Dan Brady of Watertown NYS. Legislature Chairman, Governor Rockefeller and Vincent J. DiMattina NY Comdr (Roll 623A, Frame 6-7)
      - Left to right, Dan Brady, Governor Rockefeller, DiMattina and Gordon Howe, Monroe County Manager (Roll 623A, Frame 8)
      - Left to Right, Dan Brady, Governor Rockefeller, DiMattina and Herbernt C. Brian of Ogdensburg, NY (Roll 623A, Frame 9)
      - Left to right, Mrs. Helen Murphy of Albany, Ladies Aux. President for NYS., Governor Rockefeller and Mrs. Gertrude Rhind of Wilmington Del. Past National Pres of VFW Aux (Roll 623A, Frame 10-11)
    - Governor talks to Thurston Foster Sr. of Schenectady NY (Roll 623B, Frame 1)
    - Governor waves to crowd (Roll 623B, Frame 2)
    - Governor speaks at dinner at left is DiMattina (Roll 623B, Frame 3)
    - Governor speaks at dinner, seated are J. Mallory Loos, Pres of VFW Convention Corp, unidentified man said to me a Mr. Bennett and Mrs. Helen Murphy Aux State President (Roll 623B, Frame 4)
    - Governor speaking and being congratulated by DiMattina after speech (Roll 623B, Frame 5-7)
    - Governor signs autographs as he leaves dinner (Roll 623B, Frame 8)
    - left to right, Mrs. Rand finger of Patchogue LI, Governor, Mrs. Shirley Zeller of Lindenhurst LI and DiMattina (Roll 623B, Frame 9)
    - Left to Right, Rochester Police Officers J.J. Donlon and E.J. Bastian, Deputy Sheriff G.A. VanNeal and Governor, at airport as he left Rochester (Roll 623B, Frame 10)
    - Left to right, State Police Sergeant John J. Nacca, Major Ed Galvin, Trooper Richard Moriarty and Governor Rockefeller at airport as he left for Westchester (Roll 623B, Frame 11)